zipdial.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy policy | ZipDial

## Privacy Policy

#### ZipDial Mobile Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

ZipDial knows that you, the user, care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting ZipDial’s web site [www.zipdial.com], submitting information or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

#### What does this privacy policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers ZipDial’s treatment of your personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that ZipDial gathers when you are accessing ZipDial’s web site or when you use ZipDial’s services. The types of Personal Information collected may include your full name, address, e-mail address, phone or other communication device number and other data related to your account (including contact lists and preferences). Also, this Policy covers ZipDial’s treatment of any Personal Information that ZipDial’s business partners or customers share with ZipDial. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that ZipDial does not own or control, or to individuals that ZipDial does not employ or manage. 

#### What Personal Information does ZipDial collect?

The information we gather from users enables us to personalize and improve our services. We collect the following types of information from our users. 

#### Personal Information you provide to us.

We may receive and store any information you enter on our web site or in connection with our services or that you provide to us in any other way. It is important to note that we only store Personal Information provided to use ZipDial services. For example, if you link your mobile number to your Twitter account through ZipDial, we do not store your Twitter password; it is only used by Twitter to authorize a one-time linkage with ZipDial. The Personal Information you provide may be used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain services, customizing the content you see, and communicating with you about the services and anything else that you might opt-in for. 

#### Personal Information collected automatically.

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our web site or services. ZipDial may choose to automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. ZipDial may also choose to automatically collect information from your use of the services, including account activity (e.g. storage use, number of log-ins, number of calls, phone numbers dialed), data displayed and clicked on, and other usage information (e.g. the identity of your mobile operator, your mobile subscriber circle, subscription and response data while using ZipDial services). This type of data allows us to improve and personalize our services and content delivered to you. ZipDial will not share any of your Personal Information including mobile number, individual profile information, individual usage data or any data generated while linking third party services through ZipDial, with any third party, business partner or customer of ZipDial that did not previously store such information, except as described below. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate, not individual specific, information to our partners about how our users and customers, collectively, use our site and mobile services and about the collective responses and opinions of our users and customers as expressed through use of our services. 

#### Communications

We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail or text message if your computer or phone or other communication device supports this type of program. We may also compare our user and/or customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our users. If you have subscribed to any ZipDial mobile services, ZipDial will provide you a toll free number to dial in and OPT OUT of the service. You may dial that number at any time if you wish to discontinue receiving SMS communications for a particular ZipDial service.. ZipDial fully supports and complies with TRAI regulations regarding SMS services, notifying customers at least every 6 months of how they may opt out of an SMS alerts service. 

#### What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we may transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site and on our service are visited and by how many people. ZipDial cookies do not collect Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or to identify your screen name or e-mail address. Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of  
ways. 

#### Will ZipDial share any of the Personal Information it receives?

Personal Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We may share your Personal Information only with your consent to our customers in respect of whom you have chosen, or in respect of whom you have acted upon, to use the services of ZipDial (For example, if you dial a ZipDial number after seeing an ad for company X that says something such as ‘ZipDial 080xxxxxxxx and we’ll call you back’ or ‘ZipDial 080xxxxxxxx for more information’ you are providing consent to ZipDial to share your phone number to company X) or to business partners and affiliates as described below: 

**Agents:** We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, ZipDial’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purpose. 

**Business partners and customers:** In some cases we may enter into business partnership arrangements wherein we will share your Personal Information with such partner only to enable such partner to integrate its technology with ZipDial’s technology and render its own services bundled with our services. This would include services like Customer Feedback, where you have already provided your Personal Information to a ZipDial customer. Unless you are previously notified, all business partners will treat your information in the same manner as ZipDial under this policy. However, ZipDial is not responsible for monitoring or enforcing each customer’s handling of your Personal Information. As for our customers, in cases where you utilize the services of ZipDial pursuant to any advertisement of any of ZipDial’s customer to know more about the advertising customer or his/its products/services, your Personal Information may be shared with such customer of ZipDial as already detailed previously. Each customer is responsible for following TRAI rules protecting against further contact and spamming. 

**Business Transfers:** In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user / customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if ZipDial, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, user / customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of ZipDial may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy. 

**Protection of ZipDial and Others:** We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with any law or regulation; enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of ZipDial, our employees, our customers, or others. 

**Compliance with law enforcement and judicial authorities:** We shall be bound to disclose Personal Information in response to a request/summons from a law enforcement authority; a court of law; or a quasi-judicial body. 

#### What choices do I have?

As stated previously, you can always unsubscribe (opt-out) from any ZipDial services which you were previously using. As explained earlier, the majority of browsers allow you to monitor and restrict our use of cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of some of our services or web site features. 

#### Effective date of this privacy policy

This policy is effective from the date you access this Privacy Policy or the services of ZipDial. All personal and confidential information collected is maintained and treated in the manner set forth in this policy. If you disagree with the treatment of your personal information as per this policy, please immediately refrain from using the services on www.zipdial.com and unsubscribe from the services. 

#### Changes to this privacy policy

ZipDial may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes thereby diluting the stringency in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our web site. 

#### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at ZipDial site, please contact ZipDial customer support at [info@zipdial.com](mailto:info@zipdial.com).
